Ada Peirce McCormick papers, 1881-1978 (bulk 1920-1974)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series II: General Files, ca. 1915-1978
  - India, Independence Day celebration. 1952 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - India, Jawaharlal Nehru. 1942-1964 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - India, Kumar Goshal. 1945 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - India League. 1942-1950 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - India, Miscellaneous. 1942-1956 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - India, re: Gandhi. 1942-1948 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - India, Senators' replies. 1942 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Institute for Associated Research. 1950 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Integrity Magazine. 1946-1956 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - International Students Club. 1946-1956 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - International Rescue and Relief Committee. 1942-1956 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Iona Community (Scotland). 1947-1958 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Invert, The (about this book). 1945-1951 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Isely, Helen Sue. 1950 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - J: Miscellaneous. 1925-1964 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Jackson, Clifford Huntley. 1947-1950 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Jackson, Georgia Belle. 1948-1952 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Jacobs, E. L. 1949-1953 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Jacobsen, Regina S. 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Jacobson, Frederick A. 1948-1949 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Jacome, Alex J. 1946-1963 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Jailers Institute. 1949 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Jailers Institute (audiograph recordings). 1960 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - James, Concha Romero. 1942 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - James, Richard. 1951-1957 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - James, William (copy of manuscript at Harvard). No date (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - James, William and children. 1938-1963 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Jamison. 1946-1947 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Japan. 1947-1957 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Jaqua, Gwendolyn E.. 1948-1955 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Jenkins, Dick. 1940-1957 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Jennings, Duncan. 1952-1954 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Jessey, Cornelia. 1949 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Magazines. 1949 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Jewish, Miscellaneous. 1946-1961 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, Dr. Wendell. 1956-1963 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Enid. 1963-1966 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, Marvin D. (Swede). 1964-1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Reverend John H. 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Johnson, Reverend Wilbur. 1964-1971 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Johnston, Leslie. 1949-1950 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Jones, Eugene Kinckle. 1945-1950 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Jones, Gerald. 1940-1970 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Jones, Ralph and Mildred. 1945-1946 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Jordan, Fred. 1944-1949 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Jordan, Richard (Robert Patterson). 1943-1947 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Joshi, Ansuya. 1947-1948 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Julian Press. 1953 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Just, T. Duncan. 1945-1947 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - K: Miscellaneous. 1942-1964 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Kahn, Hannah. 1946-1953 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Kane, Fan. No Date (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Keith, Frances Clark (Mrs. Richard). 1933-1966 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Keller, Helen. 1942-1971 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Kelley, Edith Gresham. 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Kelley, Reverend Alden Drew. 1942-1945 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Kemmler, Carolyn. 1946 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Kempner, Ronald. 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Kennedy, John F. 1961 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Kiersch, Jane. 1948-1949 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - King, Elizabeth. 1947-1961 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - King, Isabella Greenway. 1928-1975 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Kinsolvinga, Bishop Arthur B. 1939-1961 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Kipp, Laurence J. 1947 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Kirmse, Evelyn Jones. 1933-1971 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Kirstein, Lincoln. 1945-1946 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Kleeman, Rita Halle. 1943-1947 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Klyce, Laura Kent. 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Knight, Margaret A. 1944-1967 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Knopf, Alfred. 1948-1953 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Knoth, Frederick and Doreen. 1953-1954 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Koestler, Arthur. 1954-1955 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Kohlberg, Arthur. 1952-1954 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Koo, Dr. T. Z. 1949 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Kossack, Reverend Herman A. 1960-1961 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Kostalas, George. 1950-1953 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Kostka, William re: feature story about APM. 1949-1950 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Kramer, Max (Oscar Bosker). 1949-1954 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Kraus Reprint Corporation. 1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Kreitner, Reverend Keith and Dusty. 1961-1973 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Kreyche, Dr. Robert. 1963-1973 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Kriss, Anne. 1964 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood and Marcella. 1950-1970 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Kulikauskas, A. 1950-1953 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Kunkel, Mrs. Harvey. 1952 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Kustudick, Yvonne. 1948-1949 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Kyle, John and Peggy. 1962-1973 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - L: Miscellaneous. 1938-1971 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Labor League for Human Rights. 1943-1944 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Lackland, General Frank. 1942 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Ladies Home Journal. 1924-1950 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Laflin, Louis E. Jr. 1941-1945 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Land, The. 1945-1954 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Lane, Alfred C. 1944-1947 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Language Bank. 1969-1973 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Larsen, Ainy Farley. 1945-1948 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Latin-America (Consul at Lima). 1951 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Latter Day Saints. 1943-1964 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Laubach, Frank. 1945-1967 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Lawrence, Mrs. D. H. 1945-1946 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Layer, Mrs. Presley. 1951-1953 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Layman, W, A. 1946 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - League of Women Voters. 1942-1958 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - LeCompte, Zora. 1950 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Lee, Barbara. 1950 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Lee, Carlton R. 1941-1961 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Lennon, Florence Becker. 1949 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Leonard, Dr. Hemen B. 1955 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Leonard, Mrs. John. 1948-1949 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Leprosy. 1943-1971 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Le Rogers, Roger. 1966-1972 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Lesher, C. Zaner and Madge. 1931-1972 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Lessere, Samuel E. 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Letter. 1944-1947 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Liaison in Neighborhood Knowledge. 1969-1972 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Libraries, Miscellaneous correspondence. 1943-1955 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Library, Alderman Library. 1945-1951 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Library, Cleveland Public Library. 1944-1949 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Library, Denver Public Library. 1946-1954 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Library, Gandhi Memorial Library. 1950 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Library, Mathews Library. 1946-1961 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Library of Congress. 1943-1953 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Library of International Relations. 1960-1961 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Library, University of Denver Library. 1950 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Licenses, Character - Intelligence. 1969 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Life magazine. 1937-1970 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - The Liquorian. 1949-1950 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Lilienthal, Alfred M. 1954 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Lilly, Othelia. 1950-1953 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Lin, Bob. 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Lippincott, J.B. and Co. 1946-1954 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Lippman, Walter. 1943-1944 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Litante, Judith. 1949-1960 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Little-Brown Publishing Co. 1944-1953 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Little Chapel of All Nations. 1956, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Little Magazines. 1946-1947 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Little, Robert P. 1951-1959 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Liturgical Arts Society. 1950-1956 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Lloyd, W.W. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Locke, Alain L. 1943-1954 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Locke, Anne. 1943-1950 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Logan, Harlan. 1948-1949 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Long, Haniel. 1942-1950 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Longmans, Green and co. 1942-1948 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Look Magazine. 1952-1954 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Lord, Dr. Edith. 1949-1951 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Lose, Phoebe Starr. 1942-1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Luce's Press Clipping Bureau. 1943-1954 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Ludington, Flora B. 1947-1950 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Luitweiler, Bob. 1948-1950 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Lusby, David. 1936-1971 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Lusby, W.J. and family. 1942-1969 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Mc: Miscellaneous. 1931-1967 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - McBride, Richard R. 1950-1951 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - McCarthy, Sen. Joseph. 1950-1954 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - McCormick, Anne O'Hare and Francis. 1945-1951 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - McCormick, J. Byron and Rachel. 1946-1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - McCormick, William C. Jr. 1957-1961 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - McCourt, Mrs. Walter Edward. 1954-1955 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - McCrossen, Helen C. 1943-1946 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - McCullough, Esther. 1947-1951 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - McDonald, Dr. James. 1960-1961 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - McFarland, Ernest. 1942-1958 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - McGee, Dr. Glenn. 1955-1961 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - McInnes, Dr. John. 1952-1966 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - McKinney, Benjamin J. 1942-1956 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - McMillan, Samuel C. 1961-1972 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - M: Miscellaneous. 1923-1970 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - MacDowell Colony. 1926-1973 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - MacMillan Co. 1931-1943 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - MacMillan Co. 1944-1972 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Macrorie, Ken. 1948-1949 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Magaw, James. 1945 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Magazine Intelligence. 1947 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Magazine Tucson. 1948-1950 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Magda (prison poet). 1947 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Mager, Mrs. Winthrop M. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Magner, Frank. 1949 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Mahoney, May. 1953-1958 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Maisonville, Jeanne Alix. 1951-1952 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Malsbury, Charlotte. 1952-1962 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Manchester, Dr. Frederick. 1948 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Mann, Klaus. 1943 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Mann, Nathalie Harris. 1944-1945 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Mansfield, Chrissy V. 1943-1957 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Margaret, Sister Mildred. 1944-1946 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Marshall, Louise F. (Marshall Foundation). 1930-1951 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Marshall, George. 1941-1944 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Martin, Billie Eckert. 1948-1949 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Martin, Douglas D. 1946-1965 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Martin, George Madden. 1944 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Mather, Kirtley, Dr. and Mrs. 1952-1959 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Mathews, William R. 1942-1969 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Matthews, Jack H. 1956 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Matsumoto, Keiko. 1961-1966 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Maxwell, Robert. 1951-1972 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Maxwell, Robert, re: ideas for Letter. 1951 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Mayer, Philip and Eleanor. 1947-1948 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Mayer, Stanley. 1943-1947 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Mays, Dr. Benjamin. 1945-1956 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Mead, Dr. Albert, correspondence. 1951-1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Mead, Dr. Albert, photographs, clippings, publications. No Date (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Mead, Dr. Albert, Mead Award. No Date (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Mead, Dr. Albert, "Sex Life of the Snail." (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Menninger, Dr. Karl. 1945-1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Meldrum and Fewsmith. 1946 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Merchant, Jane. 1948-1949 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Metzger, Dr. Jeremiah. 1947 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Metcalf, Eleanor. 1943-1944 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Meyer, Dr. Karl F. 1949-1958 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Michaels, Ann. 1946 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Midtown Galleries. 1947-1950 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Miller, Alice Duer and Harry Miller. 1942-1949 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Miller, David. 1953-1954 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Miller, Ralph and Elizabeth. 1947-1955 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Miller, Ruth McCormick (Bazy). 1943-1962 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Minnick, James Wallace. 1947-1948 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Mitchell, Bishop Walter. 1937-1961 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Mobile Chronicle. 1948-1949 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Modell, Merriam (Evelyn Piper). 1951 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Molloy, John. 1952-1972 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Monroe, Mrs. Marshall (Edna). 1944-1946 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Montgomery Ward. 1945-1965 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Moore, Frank. 1949-1951 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Moore, Juanita. 1944-1948 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Moors, Mrs. John (Ethel). 1942-1946 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Morehouse College. 1945-1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, Anne. 1936-1944 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Morgan, Lucci Campell. 1939-1971 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Mori, Toshio. 1949-1950 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Morris, Mrs. Edward. 1930-1969 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Morris, Mabel. 1948-1976 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Morris, Samuel. 1967 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Morrison, Lillian. 1956-1965 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Morrow, Robert and Betty. 1941-1970 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Moser, Edna. 1945-1966 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Moses, Marion. ca. 1939-1949 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Mother Susanna (Saint Margaret's Convent). 1917-1960 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Mountain States Telephone and Telegraph Co. 1944-1963 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Muir, Larry. ca. 1944 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Mukibi, Juliana. 1964-1965 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Muller, Dr. James Arthur. 1942-1945 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Murdock, John R. 1940-1952 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Muslin World. 1948-1968 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - N: Miscellaneous. 1949-1966 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Nagler, Moses and Reisie (immigration appeal). 1941 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Narcotics. No Date (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Nation. 1944-1952 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People. 1941-1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - National Association of Magazine Publishers. 1950-1951 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - National Association for Better Radio and TV. 1954-1970 (Box 49, Folder 7-9)
  - National Audience Board. 1963 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - National Child Labor Committee. 1941-1958 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - National Committee for Peaceful Alternatives. 1951 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews. 1945-1965 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - National Council of American Soviet Friendship. ca. 1946 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ in USA. 1941-1959 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - National Council of Women of USA. 1942 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - National League of Women voters. 1942-1945 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - National Probation and Parole Association. 1942-1959 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - National Register Publishing Co. 1946-1969 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - National Recreation Association. 1948-1951 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - National Research Council. 1950-1954 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - National Review. 1955-1960 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - National Sculpture Society (Katherine T. Hobson). 1952-1956 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - National Urban League. 1942-1949 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - National Urban League Opportunity. 1942 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - National Urban League (Tucson). 1947-1955 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - National Women's Trade Union League of America. 1942-1951 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - National Women's Trade Union League of America, Life and Labor Bulletin. 1940-1942 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Natonek, Hans. 1943-1947 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Negro College Quarterly. 1945 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Negro Digest Publishing Co. 1950-1951 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Negro, Miscellaneous. 1960 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Negro Story. 1944-1947 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Negroes, study of, Tucson. 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Negro Plaque acknowledged by APM. No Date (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Negro U.S.O. 1941-1944 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Nehru, Ambassador Braj Kumar. 1961 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Neider, charles. 1943-1945 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Nelson, Eleanor. ca. 1954-1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Newman Center. No Date (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - New Republic. 1942 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - New Subiaco Abbey. 1954 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - New York Herald Tribune. No Date (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - New York Times. 1942-1972 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - New Yorker magazine. 1942-1955 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Newsweek. 1944-1957 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Nichols, Mrs. George (Janie). 1963 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Nicodemus. 1951 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Niemoller, Pastor Martin. 1938-1958 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Niger, Africa, Visist of the President to Tucson. 1967 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Noe, Ruth (Frymire). 1950-1955 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Norwegian Embassy. 1941-1945 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Noyes, Peirrepont (Oneida Community). 1951 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Nugent, Frank. 1943-1950 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Nugent Dr. Robert L. No Date (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Nunnelly, Lela B. ca. 1967-1972 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - O: Miscellaneous. 1943-1967 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Oak, Vishnu V. 1945-1949 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Oatway, Jr., Dr William. 1946 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - O'Byran, Carl. 1951 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - O'Connell, Mary. 1938-1966 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - O'Donnell, Frances. 1955 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Odorfer, Adolf. 1947-1950 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Olden, Roger and Mariann. 1957-1967 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Old Pueblo Club. 1945-1969 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Oliver, Harriet. 1948-1951 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Olsen, Helen. 1950-1951 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Olson, Nellie. 1943-1946 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Olson, Richard C. 1955-1972 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - O'Mara, Roger. 1943-1975 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Ong, Reverend Walter J. 1945-1958 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Organizations objected to by the Attorney General. 1953 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Organizations to which APM belonged. 1961, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Ortega, Dr. Joaquin. 1947 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Osborn, Sydney, re: Negro and Japanese problems. 1942-1948 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Owen, Paul. 1950 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - P: Miscellaneous. 1931-1968 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Pack, Arthur N. 1952-1960 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Paget, James. 1958 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Pai, Padmanabba. 1959 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Painter, Helen and Anne. 1943-1972 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Painter, Mrs. Thayer (Budge). 1937-1953 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Pakistan Embassy. 1950-1951 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Palmer, Parker. 1945-1949 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Pandit, Madam. 1944-1967 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Panos, Dimitrios. 1946-1948 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Pantheon Books. 1945-1974 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Parent-Teacher Association. 1950-1961 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Parker, George (Parker Brothers). 1944-1946 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Parkman, Francis. 1942-1945 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Passano, Lillie M. 1940 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Patten, Harold A. 1949-1954 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Pattison, Dr. Sidney and family. 1935-1964 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Paulding Gouverneur. 1949-1952 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Pawley, Eugene. 1950-1960 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Paylore, Patricia. 1931-1971 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Pearson, Drew. 1944-1945 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Pease, Rollin. 1955-1959 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Peck, Ann. 1965 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Pen and Brush. 1925-1970 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Pepper, Claude. 1942-1943 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Pepsi-Cola company. 1944-1945 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Permissions granted (to print in Letter, etc.) 1945-1954 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Perry, Bernard P. 1944 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Perry, Frances M. ca. 1931 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Phillips, H.M. 1950-1951 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Phoenix Chamber of Commerce. 1943-1962 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Phoenix Indian School. 1948 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Phylon. 1944-1951 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Pierce, George and Daisy. 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Pierce, Paul. 1969 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Pierce, Sally Woodcock. 1945-1946 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Pillsbury, Dorothy. 1944-1952 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Piltdown Man. 1955 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Pima County Association for Mental Health. 1952-1973 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Pima County Democratic Committee. 1952-1971 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Pima County Homemakers, Club History. 1947-1952 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Pima Hall Protest. 1938 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Pinchot, Gertrude (Mrs. Amos). 1938 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Pittsburgh Courier. 1943-1946 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Pittsburgh Public Schools. 1947 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Planned Parenthood. 1935-1974 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Pocono People's College. 1925-1930 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Poinsett, Alex. 1951 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Polish Information Center. 1941-1942 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Politics Magazine. 1945-1951 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Poll Tax Bill, Arizona. 1943 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Pond, Florence. 1938-1947 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Popenoe, Paul. 1931 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Poplar, Murcie. 1945-1950 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Potter School (Sue and Dickson Potter). 1940-1974 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Powel, Harford. 1942-1947 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Powell, Clarence Alva. 1946-1950 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Practical Anthropology. 1963 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Pratt, Wallace E. and Iris. 1956-1969 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Press clipping Bureaus. 1944-1947 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Preview/Proof. 1949-1954 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Price, E. Melville. 1946-1947 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Price, Ella Tarbell (Mrs. Paxton). 1938-1974 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Price, Mary. 1944-1948 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Price, Nellie. 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Princess Margaret. 1955 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Princeton University. 1948-1972 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Printer's Ink. 1943 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Printing. 1943-1955 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Prisons. 1943-1949 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Progressive Farmer. 1943-1947 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Public Accomodations Bill. 1960 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Public Relations News. 1946-1962 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Publishers Weekly. 1946-1950 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Puknat, Siegfried. 1951 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Pulliam talking. 1947 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Pulse Magazine. 1943-1948 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Putnam's (G.P.) Sons. 1944-1970 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Pyle, J. Howard. 1943-1950 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Quarto Magazine. 1950 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Quinlan, Roy. 1945-1947 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - R: Miscellaneous. 1937-1969 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Radcliffe College. 1942-1947 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Radio, Miscellaneous. 1947-1952 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Rainey, Arch. 1948 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Random House. 1944-1954 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Rapp, John. 1969 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Reader's Digest. 1939-1966 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Regnery Co., Henry. 1949-1973 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Reid, Gene, Tucson City Parks. 1961-1963 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Reil, Rita. 1953 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Reilly, William (Don Olcott). 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Reissig, Dr. Frederick. 1947 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Religion in Life Magazine. 1957-1958 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Religion in Life Week Brochures. 1956-1968 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Religious Book Club. 1957-1961 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Rennebohn, Oscar. 1947 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Rentschler, Gordon and Mary. 1942-1943 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Renwick, William G. and Mary. 1952-1960 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - The Reporter Magazine. 1946-1955 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Reynal and Hitchcock. 1944 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Reynolds and Son, Paul. 1930-1950 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Rhoades, Katherine Nash. 1951-1952 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Rhodes, Dr. Herbert D. 1954-1956 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Rice, Paul North. 1948 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Richard, Frederic D. 1950-1951 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Richart, Bette. 1947-1949 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Richart, Bette. 1950 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Richart, Bette. 1950-1952 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Richart, Bette, poems. 1950-1951 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Richart, Bette, prose. 1951 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Richart, Fred W. 1949-1950 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Richey, Thamar, drawing by APM. 1937 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Ridenour, G.H. 1945-1951 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Riesen, Emil. 1945-1950 (Box 57, Folder 9)